Guide to the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Issues and Programs, 1966-2010
  - Subseries IV.2. Environment and Energy, 1979-1980, 1999-2010
    - Global Warming Shareholders’ Campaign (GWC or GWSC)
      - American Standard, 2002-2006 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Apache Corporation, 2004-2008 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Auto Sector Media, 2003-2006 (Box 63, Folder 18)
      - Autos, 2002-2008 (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - Autos Media, 2003-2006 (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - BP Dialogue, 2003-2007 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Building Sector, 2004-2006 (Box 63, Folder 21)
      - Carbon Migration, 2004-2006 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Chevron-Texaco Dialogue, 2003-2008 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - Climate Denial, 2004-2008 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Finance/Insurance Media, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 22)
      - Financial Sector, 2003-2006 (Box 63, Folder 23)
      - Financial Sector Working Group, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 24)
      - Ford Motor Company Dialogue, 2003-2008 (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - General Electric Dialogue, 2002-2003 (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - General Motors Dialogue, 2003-2009 (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - Insurance, 2004-2007 (Box 63, Folder 25)
      - Investor Outreach, 2003-2006 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Kyoto Protocol, 2003-2007 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Legal Liability, 2003-2007 (Box 63, Folder 26)
      - Manufacturing/Appliances, 2004-2005 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Media
        - Climate Science, 2004-2007 (Box 36, Folder 14)
        - Extreme Weather, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 15)
        - Kyoto, 2003-2005 (Box 36, Folder 16)
        - Social Responsible Investing (SRI) / Corporate, 2002-2008 (Box 36, Folder 17)
        - U.S. Energy Policy, 2003-2010 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Oil Sector Research, 2003-2009 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Resolutions, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - SEC Working Group, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Global Warming Working Group (GWWC)
      - Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITS)/Green Buildings, 2002-2007 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Talking Points, 2001-2005 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Heinz (H.J.) Company, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Hewlett Packard (HP), 2003 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - International Finance Corporation (IFC), 2004-2007 (Box 85, Folder 32)
    - International Law--War and Environment, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 33)
    - International Monetary Fund (IMF), 2004-2007 (Box 85, Folder 34)
    - Iraq
      - Invasion and Occupation, 2003-2007 (Box 85, Folder 35)
      - Torture; Spying; Human Rights; U.S. Law, 2006 (Box 85, Folder 36)
      - War Profiteers, Economic Impacts, 2003-2008 (Box 85, Folder 37)
    - Johnson & Johnson, 2002 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Love Canal, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Marathon Oil Corporation, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Militarism
      - Agent Orange (Dioxins), 2003 (Box 85, Folder 38)
      - Environmental Impacts (General), 2003 (Box 85, Folder 39)
      - Military Pollution, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 40)
    - Monsato, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Newmont Mining, 2004-2008 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Occidental, 2008 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Oil
      - Environmental and Health Impacts, circa 2006 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Exploitation
        - Ecuador, 2003-2006 (Box 78, Folder 4)
        - Nigeria, 2003-2007 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - PepsiCo Inc., 2003 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Valero Energy Corporation, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Voluntary Action Programs, 1992, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 41)
    - Walmart Stores, Inc. (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Water and Food
      - General, 2006-2008 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Food Irradiation--Morris and Daly, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - Resolutions, 2006, 2008 (2 Folders) (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Weyerhaeuser, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Subseries IV.3. Human Rights/Labor Rights/Global Accountability Programs, 1996-2011
    - Forced Child Labor--Cotton in Uzbekistan, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Global Reporting Initiative--Apparel-Footwear Sector Supplement, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Independent Monitoring Working Group (IMWG), 1996-2001 (2 Folders) (Box 35, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Press Releases (ICCR)--Human Rights and Labor Rights, 2004-2010 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Principles for Global Corporate Responsibility, 1998-2003 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      (ICCR Publication. Includes correspondence and two editions of the publication.)
    - Project Kaleidoscope--Reports, 2005-2006 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Resources--ICCR Global Accountability, 2003-2005 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - United Nations Special Report--Business and Human Rights, 2004-2010 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Walmart Materials, 1999-2007 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - White House Apparel Industry Partnership, 1996 August-1998 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Subseries IV.5. Militarism and Violence, 1990-2007
    - General, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Articles, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Arms Manufacturing/Sales--Articles, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Budget--Militarism--ICCR & U.S., 1999-2001 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Corrections Corporation (AM:CCA) (Prison Realty Trust), 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Cost of War, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - CVS--Violence in the Workplace, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Guns
      - Articles, 1999-2001 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Charts, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Interest Group, 1999-2005 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - IRRC
      - Military and Nukes--General, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Reports--General, 1998-2002 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - International Arms Trade, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Landmines, 1993-1999 (2 Folders) (Box 53, Folder 12 to 13)
    - McDonnell Douglas, 1978-1997 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Media Violence
      - Articles, 1993-2002 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Churches’ Role Statements, 1997-2000 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Computer Games, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Lawsuits, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Letters, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Studies, 1993-1998 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Television Violence
        - General, 1995-1996 (Box 54, Folder 15)
        - Television Violence and Violent Behavior (ICCR Report), 1995 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Militarism
      - General, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Annual General Meeting (AGM), 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Charts, 2005-2007 (Box 54, Folder 22)
      - Database, 2004-2005 (Box 54, Folder 23)
      - Packets, 1999-2000 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Resolutions, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Steering Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Militarism and Violence
      - General, 1995-1997 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - Handouts, 1996 September (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - Network Catholic Lobbying Group, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Resolution, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Military
      - Charts, 1998-2001 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - Sales--Offsets, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 25)
      - Textron--Foreign Military Sales, 1986-2001 (Box 53, Folder 26)
      - Resolutions, History of Military, 1991-2001 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Motorola--Landmines, 1994-1998 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - National Rifle Association (NRA), 1999 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Nuclear Arms, 1999-2002 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Nuclear Waste, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Nuclear Weapons
      - Companies, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 32)
      - Long Term Stewardship (LTS), 2001 (Box 53, Folder 33)
      - Production, 2001-2003 (2 Folders) (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - October 12-14th Activities, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Offsets
      - Articles, 1994-2001 (3 Folders) (Box 53, Folder 36 to 38)
      - Companies, 1999-2001 (Box 53, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 40)
      - Packet, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 41)
      - Resolution, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 42)
      - Sub-Committee, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Plutonium / Tritium, 1998-1999 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Prisons--Privatization, 1998-2002 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Raytheon, 1993-1995 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Small Arms, 1998-2001 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Space Weaponization
      - General, 1999-2001 (Box 53, Folder 48)
      - Anti-Ballistic Missile (ABM) Treaty, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 49)
      - New York Times Article, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 50)
      - Resolution, 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Toys (Box 54)
      - Articles, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Letters to Retailers, 1998-2001 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Uranium
      - Depleted Uranium, 1999-2005 (Box 54, Folder 24)
      - Depleted and Otherwise, 1999-2001 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Weapons Resolutions, circa 1979-1990 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Working Groups
      - Militarism and Violence Working Group
        - Mission Statement, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 6)
        - Meeting, 1997 February (Box 54, Folder 7)
        - Minutes, 1995 1997 September-1999 November (2 Folders) (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Violence and Militarization in Society (VM)
        - General, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 14)
        - Allied-Signal--1990 Shareholder Action on Military Contracts, 1980-1990 (Box 104, Folder 1)
        - Boeing, 1999-2000 (Box 104, Folder 2)
        - Combustion Engineering--1990 Shareholder Action on Biological and Chemical Weapons, 1982-1990 (Box 104, Folder 3)
        - Computer Sciences Corporation, 2001-2002 (Box 104, Folder 4)
        - General Electric (GE)--Violence, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 17)
        - Listserv, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 15)
        - Lockheed Martin, 1990-2007 (Box 104, Folder 5)
        - Militarism, 2003-2006 (2 Folders) (Box 102, Folder 3 to 4)
        - Militarism/Depleted Uranium, 1995-2008 (6 Folders) (Box 102, Folder 5 to 10)
        - Resolution, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 16)
        - Television Violence, 1995-1999 (Box 103, Folder 18)
        - Textron, 1980-1997 (Box 104, Folder 6)
        - TRW, 1997-2002 (5 Folders) (Box 104, Folder 7)
        - United Technologies, 1997-2002 (Box 104, Folder 8)
        - Violent Video Games
          - General, 2000-2006 (2 Folders) (Box 102, Folder 11 to 12)
          - Articles, 2004-2006 (Box 102, Folder 13)
          - National Institute on Media and the Family (NIMF), 2005 (Box 102, Folder 14)
          - General, 2000-2007 (5 Folders) (Box 103, Folder 1 to 5)
          - Child’s Play, 2000-2004 (Box 103, Folder 6)
          - Entertainment Software Rating Board (ESRB), 2001-2007 (Box 103, Folder 7)
          - Government, 2004-2004 (Box 103, Folder 8)
          - International Game Developers Association (IGDA), 2001-2005 (Box 103, Folder 9)
          - Paul, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 10)
          - Photos, circa 2005 (Box 103, Folder 11)
          - Special Event, 2006 (Box 103, Folder 12)
          - Take Two Initiative (TT2), 2005-2009 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-2005 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Subseries IV.6: South Africa, 1966-1996
    - 80s Articles Archive (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - American Cyanamid, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - American Express, 1990-1991 (3 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 2 to 4)
    - American Express Bank, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - American Home Products, 1987-1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Articles on South African Corporations and ICCR, 1986-1993 (15 Folders) (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - AT&T
      - General, 1986-1991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Olivetti, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Letter from Robert Scannell to Mrs. Elen Cooke Re: Shareholder Proposal in AT&T’s 1992 Proxy Material, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Baker Hughes, 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Baltimore Court Case on South Africa, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Bandag, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Bank of America, 1985-1994 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Bank Loans and South Africa, 1977-1982 (2 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Bank Resolution Speeches, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Banks
      (See Also: Files on individual banks)
      - Banks and South Africa, 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Banks and South Africa--Miscellaneous Reports, 1966-1975 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Campaigns
        - 1966-1969 (Box 33, Folder 14)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 15)
        - 1991 (Box 25, Folder 43)
        - Campaign on Foreign Banks, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 44)
        - International Bank Campaign--Press, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 45)
      - Divestment of South African Investments, A Legal Analysis, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Frankfurt Documents on Loans to South Africa, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Howard, Bill (William Howard)
        - Bank Loans, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 24)
        - Letter to European Churches on Bank Loans, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - International Church Actions, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Kinsolving, Lester, 1972-1978 (Box 33, Folder 28)
      - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1976-1985 (Box 33, Folder 29)
      - Smith’s Statement to the Foreign Affairs Committee, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 30)
      - U.S. Bank Loans, circa 1983 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Board, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Boeing, 1989-1993 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Bristol Myers
      - General, 1986-1994 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Executive Committee / Business Conduct, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Buthelezi, Gathsa, 1976-1979 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Chase Manhattan
      - General, 1971-1978 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Annual General Meeting, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Chemical Bank
      - General
        - 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 11)
        - 1987-1993 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Chemical Bank / Martin Luther King Day Rally, 1993 January 15 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Meetings: Chemical South Africa Corporate Responsibility (SACR) Exchange, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Church Position Papers (and Church Divestment Packet), 1984 December (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Chevron
      - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Meetings with Management, 1998-1994 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Sales to Police and Military, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Citibank
      - General, 1982-1985 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Analysis of Citibank and South Africa, 1972-1976 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Citibank and South Africa Background Documents, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Divestments, 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Letter, 1986 December 10 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - New Loans, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Packet, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Press Coverage, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Riverside Church--Citibank Withdrawal, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Withdrawal Pledges, 1980-1982 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Citicorp
      - Actions
        - 1972-1973 (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 14 to 15)
        - 1977-1979 (3 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Annual General Meeting, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Divestment, 1981-1983 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Coalition on Southern Africa (COSA), 1987-1988 (2 Folders) (Box 51, Folder 20 to 21)
    - Coca-Cola
      - General, 1987-1994 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Campaign--Institutional Stockholders, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Coke Boycott, 1987-1991 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Code, South Africa
      - Code Dialog/Resolution Teams--Master List and Updates (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Code Strategy Group, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Codes Conferences
      - Codes Conference, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - “Towards a Code of Investment: Ethics for South Africa’s International Economic Relations” (Broederstroom), 1992 February 10-13 (4 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - Codes Workshop and Support Conference (New York), 1992 November 13 (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - International Solidarity Conference (Johannesburg), 1993 February 20 (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - National Foreign Trade Council Foundation (NFTCF) Meeting (New York), 1993 May (Box 83, Folder 21)
      - World Council of Churches Conference (Amsterdam), 1993 June (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Codes of Conduct
      - African National Congress (ANC) on South African Council of Churches (SACC) Code, 1993 December (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Code Monitoring, 1991-1994 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Codes: South African Council of Churches (SACC)/South Africa Catholic Bishops Conference (SACBC), 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Platform of Guiding Principles, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - South Africa: Draft Codes, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Codes, 1991-1993 (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - Code Project Funds, circa 1990 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - South Africa Freedom Principles Outreach South African Council of Churches (SACC) Code of Conduct, 1992-1994 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - South Africa Corporate Conduct Codes, 1990-1992 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - U.S.-South Africa Business Forum, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Congress of South African Trade Unions (COSATU) Code, 1992 March (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - South Africa Freedom Principles, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - American Chamber of Commerce in South Africa (AMCHAM) Codes, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - Sullivan Statement, 1993 October 20 (Box 84, Folder 15)
      - South African Council of Churches (SACC) Code
        - South African Council of Churches (SACC) Code, 1993 July (Box 84, Folder 16)
        - Press on South African Council of Churches (SACC) Code, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 17)
        - Company Support Statements, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 18)
        - Ikageng Organizational Support Services / P&M Strategic Planner (PTY) Ltd., 1993-1994 (Box 84, Folder 19)
        - Monitoring Proposal, 1993 October (Box 84, Folder 20)
        - Q&A Fact Sheet, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 21)
        - Co-Teams, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 22)
        - Company Support Statements, 1994 February (Box 84, Folder 23)
      - CBM / Sethi Pieces, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 24)
      - Standards for Business Associates, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 25)
      - Other Codes, circa 1992 (Box 84, Folder 26)
      - Code Outreach Letter Anti-Apartheid Partner List, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 27)
      - International Code Campaign, 1992-1994 (Box 84, Folder 28)
      - Code Strategy Group Consultations, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 29)
      - Community Growth Fund, Undated (Box 84, Folder 30)
      - Ecumenical Eminent Persons Group (EEPG) of World Council of Churches (WCC) / South African Council of Churches (SACC), 1994 May (Box 84, Folder 31)
      - Sullivan and Sullivan Principles
        - Sullivan #3, 1976-1980 (Box 84, Folder 32)
        - Sullivan Principles, 1980-1987 (Box 84, Folder 33)
        - Sullivan Principles/Ratings, 1985-1987 (Box 84, Folder 34)
      - U.S. Corporate Council on South Africa, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 35)
      - 100 Companies Letter, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 36)
      - Signed Letters to Corporations in South Africa, 1988 February 26 (Box 84, Folder 37)
      - South Africa “Corporate Responsibility” Readings, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 38)
      - Delegation to South Africa (ICCR), 1991 (Box 84, Folder 39)
      - National Council of Churches (NCC)--South Africa What Does Justice Require: A Call to Action, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 40)
      - Utrecht/Code Article, 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 41)
      - Utrecht Statement, 1993 June 12 (Box 84, Folder 42)
      - Company Statements Supporting South African Council of Churches (SACC) Code, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 43)
      - Code Legislation, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 44)
      - Code: African National Congress (ANC), 1993 (Box 84, Folder 45)
      - South Africa Catholic Bishops Conference (SACBC) Code of Conduct, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 46)
      - Code Q&A/Talking Points, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 47)
      - South African Council of Churches (SACC) Code of Conduct for Business Operating in South Africa, 1993 July (Box 84, Folder 48)
    - Codes Packets/Endorsements (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Codes Publicity (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Colgate Palmolive
      - General, 1981-1994 (2 Folders) (Box 42, Folder 8 to 9)
      - Campaign, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Control Data--General Information, 1984-1988 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Corporate Responsibility, Project on, 1970-1974 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Delegation Reports, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Detroit Conference--The Auto Industry in South Africa, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Divestment Options for Concerned Institutional Investors: The South African Question, 1985 April 15 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      (Conference)
    - Dresser, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Dupont, 19871-1992 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Echlin, 1987-1988 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Eli Lilly
      - 1987-1991 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - 1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Eminent Persons Testimony, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Engelhard--Philipp, 1970-1996 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - European American Bank, 1972-1977 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Exxon--South Africa, 1986-1990 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Financial Pressures--United Nations, 1990 October 18 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Firestone, 1987-1990 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Fluor
      - General Information, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - General Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - SEC Challenge, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Focus Group--2nd Tier Companies, 1990 (2 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 9 to 10)
    - Ford Motor Company
      - Ford in South Africa
        - General, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, 1976-1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
        - Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Actions, 1977-1979 (3 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 7 to 9)
      - Open Letter to Ford Motor Company of Canada, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Labor Dispute, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Freedom Charter, 1970-1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - General Electric
      - General Information, 1988-1991 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - General Correspondence, 1986-1994 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Meeting with Company, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - General Motors
      - General Motors in South Africa
        - General
          - 1970-1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
          - 1985-1993 (Box 42, Folder 25)
        - Correspondence
          - 1970-1979 (Box 23, Folder 13)
          - 1985-1993 (Box 42, Folder 26)
        - Reports, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Actions
        - 1971-1973 (3 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 16 to 18)
        - 1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
        - General Motors Advertisement, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
        - 1977 (Box 23, Folder 21)
        - General Motors Memo on Contingency Plans for South Africa, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 22)
        - 1978-1980 (3 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 23 to 25)
      - Meetings with Company--Platform of Guiding Principles, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - South African “Spies,” 1973-1982 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Why General Motors (GM) Decided to Quit South Africa, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Gillette, 1984-1984 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Goodyear, 1989 (2 Folders) (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Gulf Oil
      - Donna’s Testimony on UN Oil Hearings, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Resolutions for Proxy Statement, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - Gulf Meeting, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - Gulf Information (Cabinda), 1970-1972 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Guidelines for Corporate Withdrawal (ICCR), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Heinz, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Hewlett-Packard (HP)
      - General, 1988-1990 (Box 42, Folder 31)
      - HP to Leave South Africa, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Honeywell, 1987-1994 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Human Rights Day
      - 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - 1988 (Box 84, Folder 49)
      - Liturgy, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - IBM
      - Shareholder Meeting--Press, 1989 April 18 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Shareholder Meeting, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Prayer Service for 1990 Shareholder Meeting, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - ICCR Proxy Challenges, 1970-1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ICCR Reports
      - A History of ICCR Resolutions on South Africa, circa 1985 (Box 51, Folder 6)